<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Welcome to KeepEarthCool.info! on KeepEarthCool.info</title><link>https://keepearthcool.info/</link><description>Recent content in Welcome to KeepEarthCool.info! on KeepEarthCool.info</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 10:50:28 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://keepearthcool.info/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://keepearthcool.info/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 10:50:28 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://keepearthcool.info/about/</guid><description>The purpose of this website is to inform and educate as many people as possible of the threat of long lasting climate change. This website will also cover the largest areas of carbon emission, as well as what you can do as an individual to contribute to tackling this difficult problem.</description></item><item><title>Climate Change in Pictures</title><link>https://keepearthcool.info/in_pictures/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://keepearthcool.info/in_pictures/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Climate Change in The News</title><link>https://keepearthcool.info/in_the_news/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://keepearthcool.info/in_the_news/</guid><description>Climate Change in the news: As climate change effects worsen, it&amp;rsquo;s discussed more every day in the news. It&amp;rsquo;s necessary and beneficial to have climate change be a big part of the current news so people aren&amp;rsquo;t left in the dark with what&amp;rsquo;s going on with their own planet. The more people that are educated on this, the better chance we have of more people doing their part. Weather events that are out of the ordinary are often the topic of discussion, and usually disrupt the surrounding life.</description></item><item><title>Emissions In The United States</title><link>https://keepearthcool.info/emissions_in_us/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://keepearthcool.info/emissions_in_us/</guid><description/></item><item><title>How does it work?</title><link>https://keepearthcool.info/how_does_it_work/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://keepearthcool.info/how_does_it_work/</guid><description>One major reason for what makes Earth so unique is its ability to support life, which is in large part due to the greenhouse effect. Life is dependent on energy, which, at the base natural level, arises from the sun. This energy heats the earth, passing through our atmosphere and heating our planet, while energy is re-radiated outward, which either leaves the atmosphere, or is captured by greenhouse gasses in the atmosphere.</description></item><item><title>Weather in the 21st Century</title><link>https://keepearthcool.info/weather/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://keepearthcool.info/weather/</guid><description>Here is some information on weather patterns changing over the past several years. Based on this data from weatherspark.com, weather is somewhat predictable, but also changing. On average, temperatures are slowly rising.
Weather and temperature in Pleasant Hill, California during the weeks of April 10 - April 16, and July 10 - July 16, in 2000, 2002, 2012, and 2022 (July weather in 2021, not 2022).
April April 10 - April 16, 2000: Temperature: H: 72, L: 47</description></item><item><title>What Can Be Done?</title><link>https://keepearthcool.info/what_can_be_done/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://keepearthcool.info/what_can_be_done/</guid><description>Now that you&amp;rsquo;re educated, you may be asking, what can be done to help? The following is a list of what can be done on the individual level, to the local, and global stage.
Organizations like the EPA are ensuring everyone from individuals to industry are falling in line with emission standards. From the private sector, leaps in solar, wind and geothermal energy provide cleaner, healthier options to fossil fuels.</description></item><item><title>What Is Climate Change</title><link>https://keepearthcool.info/what_is_climate_change/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://keepearthcool.info/what_is_climate_change/</guid><description>Climate Change broadly refers to major shifts in temperature and weather, which may be natural, or human originated. However, since the 19th century, human driven industrialization and energy demands have been the largest contributor to climate change. Evidence of Climate Change can be seen in changing temperature and rain patterns, increase in ocean temperature, acidity, and rise in sea level, melting of permafrost and ice sheets, as well as great shifts in ecosystems around the world.</description></item><item><title>Why is it Happening?</title><link>https://keepearthcool.info/why_is_it_happening/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://keepearthcool.info/why_is_it_happening/</guid><description>While massive shifts in climate have occurred in the past, such as the Roman warm period and the little Ice Age, these events only occurred on a regional scale, as opposed to the global effects of climate change seen today. Along with this, the last natural major shift in Earth&amp;rsquo;s climate occurred over 2,000 years ago. Instead, over the past two hundred years, starting with industrialization in the 1800&amp;rsquo;s, indications our climate has been changing have arisen, only this time, with examination of the amount of greenhouse gas in the atmosphere, it is clear that this is human originated.</description></item><item><title>Why Should I Care?</title><link>https://keepearthcool.info/why_care/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://keepearthcool.info/why_care/</guid><description>Having come to this point, you may be wondering, Why should I care? The following list contains reasons that it is not only important, but essential to handle this issue before it comes to late.
If not addressed, earth is predicted to rise up to 3 degrees in temperature. This would mean:
Deadlier heat waves, wildfires, freak weather events, acidic rain.
Hotter and more acidic oceans, leading to a massive decline in sea population.</description></item></channel></rss>